NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED
DURING THE FILMING OF THIS MOVIE
Osman has gone mad. Does this man thinks
he can defeat us with so little numbers?
You treacherous dog!
Archers!
2 DAYS AGO
Pretty lamb...
Come.
Oh, pretty lamb! You are a pretty lamb!
Look, wolf brother is here too.
Come, wolf brother.
A Brother who loves being
the fog's companion.
Brother who becomes
the guide on the roads.
My loves, the mystery has been solved.
The mystery has been solved!
The mystery has
been solved in Hira!
He read, he read!
The orphan of Mekkah read!
Get out of the way, for he comes!
Muhammed, whose name is beautiful comes!
Wreathe, wreathe...
Wreathe your lover! He read, he read!
The orphan of Mekkah read!
He read, and Kisrâ wavered.
He read, and the fire of the
Zoroastrians extinguished.
He read, and the tyranny ended
and the world saw the light!
What's coming, is coming!
There are roads that make the heart clear,
and the mind strong.
My heart is clear, and my mind is clean!
You didn't exist, then you did.
You existed, then you didn't.
Neither existing, or non-existing,
what matters is union.
And the union is a great state.
Hail to the men of state!
Hail to the state!
Hail!
This gate, is of state.
This gate, is of men.
With an invulnerable gate, unbreakable
wrist, heart is what a man needs.
Threes, sevens, forties!
The ones who became
one in forty! Hail to you!
May our state endure!
May the world see the light!
May the marching men
become a state to the world!
May he become the state!
Welcome.
Thank you.
Come, sit.
Pretty lamb...
Allah created humans.
He gave them wisdom, heart.
Mind's ornament is tongue, and the
tongue's ornaments are words.
I heard. It's the truth.
Everything that existed from
nothing, will cease to exist.
This thing you call life will
also pass like the wind.
I heard. It's the truth.
But, if one can hold both of his worlds
together in balance, one will find peace.
A bey is great if he obeys the tradition.
If Allah gives a Bey a blessing.
That Bey, his people and
his state will be happy.
I heard. It's the truth.
Now is the time to
unlock the heart's lock...
... and to sheathe wisdom's sword.
I've been called to peacefulness.
I came to the council, that's
whiter than the white.
My mission is to reburn our fire.
Both you, and your aim is known.
But do you know yourself?
Forgive me if I made a mistake.
One who understands, understands.
One who knows, know.
The one who knows, and
understands, gets what one wants.
From now on, the sword you carry, the
horse you ride, the bed that you sleep...
the road you walk, the dream that
you dreamt is not yours.
The time is not yours,
the place is not yours.
The son is not yours,
The breath is not yours!
Then whose are they?
They are nation's. They are nation's.
They are nation's.
The world is on fire.
It's crumbling, shattered.
The devil's army is fighting, killing.
The people are waiting for a hope from us,
they want us to act!
How do we do that?
By being a Turk, staying in Islam.
That is not anyone's,
but of a wise man's job.
Hail to my ancestor Oghuz,
to Saltuk Buğra Han...
... and from Saltuk Buğra
Han, to Alparslan...
... and to countless soldiers of heart,
And, may all our greetings go to the
Sultan of the worlds, Prophet Muhammad...
... and his followers.
Osman, son of Ertuğrul.
The devil's army is burning the world.
The Turk's army builds order.
We will build such a state, that in it,
the wolf and the lamb will be brothers.
We will build such a state, that we will
find white hair in the white milk.
We will build such a state,
that it will endure forever.
May my blood and life
be sacrificed for this state.
May my mind and heart be for this state.
Now our legend begins.
You've come and we've met.
We have met, and we have dreamt.
Our first mission is to make
our people dream of a state.
May this be such a
dream, that 72 nations...
... 7 weathers, 4 corner
unite under that dream.
May this be such a dream,
that everyone will find peace.
We passed this summer in Domaniç too.
Time runs fast.
At least our animals are fed.
And our women gathered all the plants.
They prepared winter supplies.
Who is it? Yusuf, is that you?
I'm in a deep well. Hasan, it's you!
Who is it? Whose hands are those?
These hands, these iron holding hands...
My little blacksmith, beautiful
named Ahmet's hands!
I kiss your flower gathering hands.
My valiant Ahmet. Gonca Hatun!
Give Ahmet his gift.
Here.
Are you prepared?
I helped my father but the work
is not done. There is a lot of work left.
He said we can move only
after the caravan leaves.
Why is that?
Father said, if my mother was
here, it would be easier.
Why are we here for, my Ahmet?
We will help, of course.
Gonca, you can go help,
I will come after I'm finished here.
Come Ahmet. Let's go.
Can we race? Who would win?
Come on then!
The children smell like heaven, my Bala.
Ahmet is an orphan. My heart
hurts everytime I look at him.
That's because your soft
heart wants to be a mother.
It has been some time that
you've been married to Osman, girl.
The time for you to hold your own
child on your hands has come already.
And, Osman is a son of Bey.
He can't be without a child.
Especially a boy,
The one who gives and
takes is Allah, Hazal Hatun.
Of course, of course.
But...
... you should try harder.
If it's not happening, find a cure.
Look, people talks. They say
Bala Hatun won't have a baby.
They might talk to Osman too.
They are men.
Their patience is short.
You might share your tent with
another woman in an instant.
If it is my destiny, I will live it too.
I am like your mother, girl.
If you have a problem, tell me.
It's also my responsibility
to seek a remedy.
First we move the caravan to Söğüt,
then we can talk about it later.
Inshallah.
Mashallah to my lion, mashallah!
My Ahmet, where are
you going in such a hurry.
Boran Alp, leave us,
we will go to my father.
I can help too, let's go.
Gonca Hatun will help, thank you.
It's enough for soldiers
to do their own job.
Thank you, Ahmet Alp, thank you.
Come here.
Come on, my lion.
My Bey will be there until
we migrate, right brother?
He will, inshallah, he will.
Inshallah.
Father, father!
May your father die for you!
I've brought you Gonca Hatun,
so we can prepare faster.
- Thank you, sister.
- It's nothing, brother Hasan.
Come on, let's get to work.
- Ambush!
Come on! Get the spears!
Leave no one alive! Attack!
Ahmet!
Leave your weapons.
I will leave them to you.
This year's onions are
rather bitter, uncle.
Would there be fruitfulness where
the Mongol walks, nephew?
Inshallah, when those jackals leave our
soil, onions will be the same as before.
I have around 50 Frank soldiers...
... and Nökers that escaped
from Geyhatu's wrath.
They are looking for someone
to sell their swords like me.
Why would we hire
men like you, Cerkutay?
I've heard that you took Kulucahisar.
Byzantium is hunting you.
And Geyhatu is also looking for you.
You need warriors like us.
Before we sell our swords to your enemies...
... for old times' sake...
... I came to you first.
I give an offer to you first!
Ahmet! Ahmet!
Father! Father!
Come here, don't run!
Bala Hatun!
Ahmet'
Let go!
Let me go! Bala Hatun!
We have nothing to do with the bandits
who run from the battle, and betray...
... their own army.
No problem. I made
my offer, I will not insist.
- My Bey!
- What is it, Saltuk? What happened?
Lord Alexis attacked the ones
who were returning.
Women and children,
we've lost so many, my Bey.
What are you talking about, Saltuk?
Where is Hazal and Bala Hatun?
The soldier who brought
the news said he doesn't know.
So the whole world wants to come to us.
Then let them come!
And get these out of Söğüt.
If I ever see them again...
Help the wounded!
For the love of Allah, water!
Come on!
In the name of Allah.
Castle of İnegöl
Ahmet! Ahmet! Ahmet!
Ahmet Alp! Ahmet Alp!
A valiant doesn't give up.
A warrior doesn't lose hope.
Osman Bey will save us, my lion.
He will save us.
I'm a warrior of Osman Bey.
How could I bow down to these craven?
-Mashallah. Mashallah, my lion.
-Silence!
We are the warriors of Osman Bey.
-We are the warriors of Osman Bey.
Father!
Hey!
Long-suffering and enduring people
of İnegöl!
You lost your sleep for too long...
...you were waiting in fear
for too long...
...you were grieved to hear what
happened in Kulucahisar.
Osman the Cruel and his men burned our
brothers alive!
They killed babies in their mothers'
bellies. Like it wasn't enough...
...they burned our churches!
Every place these barbarians stepped on,
turned into a blood bath.
I, the Lord of İnegöl,
Alexis...
...I brought you peace!
I took our revenge from those barbarians
in such a way that...
...they won't forget it until their
last breaths.
They paid for all the pain we suffered!
Lying pander...
Lying pander!
Where is Osman?
We want to drink wine from Osman's
skull!
Allahu Akbar.
I promise you, the head of that barbarian
will be on our pike!
I promise you, the castles that those
devils occupied will be ours again!
This isn't the place, take them away,
come on!
-What's wrong, Göktuğ?
-My Bey.
We were raided in the Domaniç uplands.
What are you saying? Who?
What panders?
Alexis. Lord of İnegöl.
What're our casualties?
Heavy, my bey.
Come on!
Where was my uncle then?
Where was Gündüz Bey?
Where were the soldiers?
What were they doing?
-Hang on. Hang on, brothers! Hang on!
-Thank you.
We will get over this too, inshallah.
-My bey.
-Huh?
Speak!
Bala Hatun...
-What happened?
-Bala Hatun is wounded, my bey.
Bala!
Bala! Bala!
Mother, my heart is burning.
Tell me she is all right!
Thank Allah, our girl is in
perfect health.
Bala...
Osman...
Bala! My love.
My heart.
-Osman.
-I'm here.
Ahmet.
-Ahmet...
-What happened to Ahmet?
They took him.
Boran too was captured.
Ahmet is without his mother, Osman.
Don't leave him alone.
Save him from that hell.
Don't worry.
With Allah's approval...
...I will make their lives unbearable.
Rest now.
Rest, so when Ahmet comes back,
he can see you healthy.
My Bala...
Move!
While slaughtering everyone else,
why did they bring us here?
They want to use us, dead or alive.
Brother.
Don't you resist them!
Stand tall, don't bow down.
Think about your child.
We will save Ahmet.
Come on.
Ahmet, stay on our back, my lion.
My lion, come on.
We won't resist them.
I wanted to see you in this rathole.
So, you are the closest warriors of
Osman Bey, huh?
Thank Allah, we are like his blood.
Were you with him...
...in Kulucahisar?
-Thank Allah that...
...we were destined to be the veterans
of that battle.
Osman...
Where is Osman?
To rip your heart off, he must be
sharpening his blade.
Father...
Father, get up, father!
Come on, father!
Get up, father!
Come on!
Father!
Get up, father! Come on, father!
Come on!
Die!
Let me go!
Let's go.
I will gift these two to Osman for
Kulucahisar.
Father!
Every single family lost someone...
...they even killed the pregnant
daughter-in-law of Sergeant İlyas.
How did we fall into such a trap, uncle?
It's not the time to grief for the
defeat, brother.
Osman is right, my nephew.
Pull yourself together.
It's time to prepare for revenge.
You are right, uncle. But when?
How?
Tomorrow. An eye for an eye,
a teeth for a teeth.
Does our tent have the strength, Osman?
Do our men or women have the power?
-Let us wait and think about it, nephew.
-What will we think about, uncle?
If we don't move now, we can never
stand up again.
We are knowingly sending the people
to death, Osman!
Let us take a breath. Get stronger,
re-organize.
So that our soldiers can heal, my nephew.
If you were so smart, you should've taken
your measures and prevented it.
If we have a weakness, so do they.
They dealt us a major blow after
a long time.
Now, they all have
the euphoria of victory.
Osman must be thinking that we have
the euphoria of victory now.
-We are.
From now, no one will take a sip.
Everyone will forget the blow we dealt,
and remember cruelty in Kulucahisar.
The ones who forget our slaughtered
children, our destroyed relics...
...should be damned...
...should be a friend to the hellhounds.
What are you thinking?
We will attack them before giving a
chance to recover.
If we give them to take a breath...
...we will be feeding our own monsters.
We will face them tomorrow.
It will be such a great battle that...
All the saints will leave their graves...
...and join our army.
Jesus will come down
to earth...
...and lead our armies.
He must've reinforced his army
with troops from Constantinople.
No doubt.
True. But...
...every army has a weakness.
His army must've rested.
And their morale is boosted.
True. It will shake us.
But, their faith will be their
biggest problem.
Osman, most of our warriors are
wounded, exhausted...
We will reach to their souls.
We will cure their wounds.
-Selamün aleyküm
-Aleyküm selam.
What's the situation, Master Davut?
Though, I know. The warriors aren't fine.
They are wounded. And a lot of
weapons are taken.
How many weapons can you make
until morning?
If you will take revenge from the enemy,
I'll make weapons out of any steel I find.
Just so we can get our revenge soon.
Don't let the path of revenge be our
end.
Revenge is a dish best eaten cold,
my nephew.
Even if not today, it will be
eaten tomorrow.
Strike while the iron is hot, Dündar Bey.
We should strike soon so that their
victory won't be abiding.
We should strike soon so that our
defeat won't be our fear.
We should strike soon so that we can
bury our pain in the ground.
Forge such weapons that our victory
will be the subject of epics.
As you command, my bey.
How are your wounds, brother?
Not as deep as the ones on my heart.
Now listen to me carefully.
All right.
Osman speaks the truth. But if we lose,
we'll return the way we came.
All the efforts, all the struggle, all the
suffering will be for nothing.
I wish we had sent word to my brother,
Yavlak Arslan.
He would come to aid with
his veterans.
We have many wounded warriors.
What if this battle is our disaster?
Be at ease, wife. Tomorrow, such a
storm will break out on those heathens...
Allah who didn't leave the valiants of
Badr alone...
...will come to our aid with the angels.
Mashallah.
Let's begin the preparations, then.
If you don't build a tower from the skulls of
the heathens tomorrow...
...I will die in disappointment.
May you live long, wife.
May you live long.
You brought honor to my tent.
Tomorrow will be a good day.
Castle of İnegöl
Osman has a death wish.
He invites our lord to a battle
to die.
Osman will die!
Guards!
With the name of Allah!
I tied your armor so tight
that...
...the heathens' weapons
can't pierce it.
I tied a knot on your steel, my bey...
...as a shield against the spikes that
seek your blood.
For every single drop of blood
they spilled...
...for every life they have taken...
...and for Ahmet...
...I'll leave them no corner to run to
in this world.
My warriors! If we fall, the nation falls!
If we get tired, the state collapses!
If we win, the enemy trembles!
My warriors!
For the love of...
...who makes many out of few...
...who gives us courage!
Today...
...it is a sin to...
...get tired, agrize, drain away...
...or give up!
It is the day of the holy war!
Come on!
Ya Allah!
Allahu Akbar.
Ahmet Alp!
Do you see it? Didn't I tell you that
Osman Bey would come?
Osman is out of his mind.
Do he think that he can beat
us with that many men?
Osman Bey!
Vile dog!
Don't stand still!
Move! Come on!
Allah!
Göktuğ!
Come on!
Die, Osman!
Charge!
Protect Ahmet!
Let's go, my lions!
Allahu Akbar!
What do we do?
Attack!
Master Davud!
When do you think we'll get some news?
How should I know?
I hope we get good news.
People are full of hope.
They want us to rise.
How will we succeed?
By being Turks
and staying Muslim.
I'd die for this state.
Nobody touches the prisoners.
Take care of the wounded.
They didn't treat us that way, my Bey!
They made us puke blood!
We should be different.
We should be different so that...
... our prophet...
... is proud of us.
Very well, my Bey.
To you...
All glory to you, my Rab(God).
All glory to you.
My dear Rab!
You gave us power!
You gave us courage.
We were helpless.
You made us powerful!
We were few,
you made us plenty.
My dear Rab!
Protect us from arrogance!
- Amin!
My dear Rab!
Thank you!
- Thank you!
- Thanks to you!
This army, this nation,
shall die for you!
- Shall die for you!
Please, accept our prayers!
- Amin!
- Please, accept our prayers!
Eternal justice,
eternal freedom!
- Allahu Akbar!
You're the only artist
I get inspirations from.
My only struggle is
to protect your legacy.
I'm fully confident that
I will succeed.
You're the greatest example of
how hard one becomes an artist.
I admire your ability
to overcome problems.
You never gave up.
Never!
Mighty Ceasar! Your greatest work
is the Roman Empire!
Your greatest work, created by
shedding the blood of the enemy...
... by showing no mercy to traitors,
heartening the cowards!
Mighty Ceasar! Rome
is fighting for its life today!
The Roman Empire is under the attack
of barbarians!
Its leaders are destroying
Rome from the inside!
I am Aya Nikola! I promise!
I'll recreate the big and
powerful Roman Empire!
Salute, soldier!
Salute the mighty Ceasar!
My magical fingers have recreated Ceasar.
Flawless.
The Emperor is waiting for you.
Mighty Ceasar...
At last...
Alexis, governor of İnegöl.
As if getting defeated by the
Kayıs is not enough...
... he ran away from the battle like a rat
and hid in his castle.
- How could he do that?
- How dare him!
What comes after Karacahisar
and Kulacahisar castles?
İznik? Bursa?
Or...
... Constantinople?
Enough!
Just like we beat the crusader
army off of our city...
... it's time we beat off
the Turks as well.
I only have one commander in my empire
who I believe can do this.
Invite him to the council.
Emperor.
Honourable members of the council.
You know why you were invited.
Because you are sick...
... and tired...
... of cowardice and betrayal!
So that I could end...
... the harassments of the enemy!
You called me so that I can introduce my
iron fist to the east of our Empire!
But...!
But...
Under two conditions.
If you allow me to...
I'll take back the Kulacahisar
Osman Bey took.
I'll also take back the Karacahisar
his father took.
But this won't annihilate
the danger of Turks.
Of course, you'll applaud,
drown me in gold and raise my rank.
But this small gift I'll be giving
you will not stop...
... our melting like snow on a mountain
summit on a hot day.
What's your offer, Nikola?
I want full command of all the governors,
soldiers, patrol units in the area.
Full authority.
Not to take back the castles
we have lost.
To take back everything...
To take back everything we have lost.
Our lands, churches, villages, bridges...
To take back the honour we have lost.
Long story short...
I want unlimited authority to take
back the spirit we have lost.
Emperor.
What about the second condition?
I gather my own men.
The leader of this team...
... will be Flatyus. Your greatest enemy.
Don't you have food?
We're hungry!
No. I can't sit here and wait.
We need a solution.
What solution?
We need a solution to quickly inform those
who are expecting news!
Master Davud!
Thank you, my Allah!
My lions!
- Praise be!
- Praise be! Thank you, my Allah!
- Move!
- Thank you, my Rab(God)!
Make way!
Are we victorious?
Thank you, my Rab!
Thank you!
May Allah bless you with many victories!
My Ahmet!
How many heathens did you slice,
my Ahmet?
I'd die for you!
Look at me.
My father became a martyr!
You are here safe and sound.
We are so grateful.
Praise be, Gonca Hatun, praise be.
Thank my Allah, who granted us with
this victory.
Amin!
My valiants!
I will cut it short.
- Thank heaven, we defeated the enemy!
- Thank heaven.
Thank heaven.
Now, we need to defeat our nafs!
(self ego)
Eyvallah.
(Thanks)
Our friendship ends here.
Forgive me.
Constantine.
My dear friend, Constantine
resurrecting!
What is happening there?
What is that?
Let me introduce you...
Constantine.
He is escaping!
Constantine, my dear friend.
I am grateful.
Nicola.
How great it is to see you after
so many years.
I guess dungeons couldn't break you.
Revenge fed me.
I came to give you a new mission.
In the day I am escaping?
Get away.
You didn't stop those viles who
put me in there!
Thank you, friend. You saved my life.
I completed my mission, Nikola.
If you don't have a command, I'd like
to return to my duty.
I used to knew every pain
you'd gone through.
I used to know every meal you'd had.
I came here.
I came here and wanted to see if my
efforts went down to drain or not.
I hope I didn't let you know.
But, don't forget that Flatyos is
nobody's dog!
Flatyus! I offer you destroying Ertuğrul
and Kayıs!
My God.
Finally...
İnegöl Castle
4 days after...
Nikola.
Emperor heard us, and sent you.
For christ's sake!
Today is going to be our salvation day.
Welcome.
Welcome my old friend.
Were they with you while you were
running away from Kayıs, Alexis?
Are you here to question us or help us?
To question you.
But not you.
It's Kayıs.
I brought you a gift, Alexis.
I hope you like it.
Thank you, Nikola.
I hope you like the meal which I
have it prepared.
It's your favourite meal, Pork stew
with beans. I didn't forget.
I like it.
Traitor!
Supreme Caesar. my first action is to
clear the idiots in our castle.
I feel honored to present you.
I don't like cowards.
Kneel in front of New İnegöl Governor
Aya Nikola!
Now it's time to clear the enemies
outside the castle.
In a short time, with my will and soul
of Helen, a brand new Roma will rise!
May Jesus bless you, Governor Nikola.
Bless all of us, father, all of us.
Bala.
What are you doing?
While I am standing here? No.
I want you to come to the table
that I prepared myself, Osman.
You are tired of fighting, please grant me
this honor.
Oooohhh...
My sweet Bala.
You already honored me by taking
a huge place in my heart.
Besides, I can set the table very well.
Come on, sit.
Osman Bey, can I?
Come.
What is new?
Ertuğrul Bey.
News from Ertuğrul Bey.
Dündar Bey invites you to his tent.
My Osman.
May it be good, my Osman.
Fast, fast, bring the clothes fast.
What's it about my father, uncle?
Kuzgun Bey from Cobanogullari.
- Welcome Kuzgun Bey.
- I have news from Ertuğrul Bey.
May Allah be pleased of you, you
brought good news from my father.
Eyvallah, Osman Bey.
(thank you)
Yavlak Arslan and Ertuğrul Bey will meet
in Kastamonu and evaluate Byzantine.
- Ertuğrul Bey is waiting in Badembükü.
- Is my brother fine?
Fine enough to break infidels.
Masha Allah.
Masha Allah. (praise be)
Then, let me set off immediately.
Ertuğrul Bey wants Osman alone.
I was commanded that.
Bey of the Beys Yavlak Hasan also wants to
see Osman who became legend in wars.
Ertuğrul Bey wants to set off from
Gündoğan tomorrow morning.
You brought happiness, Kuzgun Bey.
You made us happy.
Eyvallah, I completed my duty,
brought the news.
Excuse me.
Do you know Kidigon River, Flatyus?
The river that Julia Caesar passed with
his legions...
to become Emperor by conquering Rome.
Not Emperor.
A god.
He was a God.
His heart flows in this land's water.
In Sakarya river.
When the time comes, I will cross
that river.
That river, Flatyus...
is going to make me the Emperor of Rome.
Did I tell that I was baptized in Sakarya
River?
From that day, every river in world
flows in my body.
Just like Julia Caesar.
It resembles you more than him.
Can you spot any difference?
I can't.
What is...
Lots of death is
hidden in this little box.
First Söğüt, then Karacahisar.
First tears, and then blood will be there,
in every place Turks conquered.
Then...
Our we will climb our victory ladder,
Flatyus.
To our victory.
Are you too confused that only
Osman was invited by Ertuğrul Bey, my Bey?
Do you think he should have
invited me, Hazal?
Of course he should have, Dündar Bey.
You are Ertuğrul Ghazi's brother.
You are the honorable Bey of this tribe.
May Allah give my lifespan to my brother.
However, I don't know how I will
look at his eyes...
when he comes here.
Past is past, Dündar Bey.
If he was going to say something,
you'd know that.
Also, Ertuğrul Ghazi's compassion is as
famous as his justice.
His justice is famous too, Hatun.
I have no doubt.
However, I don't understand why Osman
goes while you are here.
You have experience, you are valiant.
Both wisdom and administration is
in Ertuğrul Ghazi.
He knows what to do the best.
My Ertuğrul Bey.
My Ertuğrul Bey is coming!
Brother!
My father.
My Father.
- Welcome, father.
- Thank you.
Welcome, brother, welcome.
I have longed for you all.
Thank you brother.
My Bey.
Where is Osman?
I can't see Osman.
- Didn't you call Osman?
- What are you talking about, Dündar?
Where is Osman?
Osman...
I thought Osman was with you, my Bey.
Why did you think that, Gündüz?
-What's happening here?
-My Bey.
Yesterday, Yavlak Arslan's chamberlain,
Kuzgun Bey was here.
He said that you summoned Osman Bey.
No one knew that I would come
to the tents.
The secret is revealed.
Cain killed Abel and the secret got
revealed.
The earth cried. It cried, indeed.
Tears became a flood.
There were the floods, the floods!
Mountains turned into islands,
plains turned into seas.
A voice was heard in the flood,
''Give me your hand, give me your hand!''
''What are you waiting for, my child?
Give me your hand!''
''Please, don't make your father sad.
''Give me your hand, son. Give me your
hand! Look, Father Noah wants you.''
''How can a father not spare his son.
Give your hand, give your hand!''
''The waves will eat you, give me your
hand! Give me your hand!''
Son didn't give his hand.
Father Noah cried.
One tear dropped into the sea.
The flood showed mercy and guided
Father Noah to security.
Hey, love, tell me.
Who is the father?
Who is the son?
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com